Research shows that in developed countries, more affluent and educated people tend to consume higher-quality diets—including more fruits and vegetables, fish and whole grains.
研究表明，在发达国家，较富裕、受教育程度较高的人往往摄入质量更高的饮食，包括更多的水果和蔬菜、鱼类以及全谷物。
In contrast, economically disadvantaged people report diets that are nutrient-poor and energy-dense.
相比之下，据经济上处于弱势的人自述，他们的饮食营养贫乏、能量密度高。
They are less likely to have food-purchasing habits that conform to public health recommendations.
他们的食物购买习惯符合公共卫生建议的可能性更小。
These dietary differences are often accompanied by higher rates of obesity and diabetes among lower-income people.
这些饮食差异往往伴随着低收入人群中更高的肥胖率和糖尿病发病率。
This relationship between social class and diet quality and health is extensively documented.
社会阶层与饮食质量和健康之间的这种关系，已有大量文献记载。
However, the research does not explain why this is the case—a question that has significant implications for designing effective policies and initiatives to improve diets and prevent chronic diseases.
然而，这些研究并没有解释为什么会这样，而这个问题对于制定有效的政策和举措以改善饮食、预防慢性病有着重大意义。
Public-health initiatives to promote healthy diets often focus on providing nutrition education and recipes.
旨在促进健康饮食的公共卫生举措往往侧重于提供营养教育和食谱。
These approaches, however, often presume less food literacy (i.e. food knowledge and skills) among low-income people.
然而，这些做法往往预先假定低收入人群的食物素养（即有关食物的知识和技能）较低。
Are unhealthy diets really the result of poor choices, limited food skills and knowledge?
不健康的饮食真的是选择不当、食物技能和知识有限的结果吗？
Research suggests that adults in food-insecure households are just as likely as those in food-secure households to adjust recipes to make them more healthy.
研究表明，食物无保障家庭中的成年人调整食谱、使其更健康的可能性，和食物有保障家庭中的成年人一样大。
They are also just as proficient in food preparation and cooking skills.
他们在备餐和烹饪技能方面也同样熟练。
There is no indication that increasing food skills or budgeting skills will reduce food insecurity.
没有迹象表明，提高食物技能或预算规划技能会减轻食物无保障的状况。
Instead, disadvantaged groups are constrained by their economic, material and social circumstances.
相反，弱势群体受制于自身的经济、物质和社会状况。
For example, low income is the strongest predictor of food insecurity in Canada, where one in eight households experiences insufficient access to nutritious foods.
例如，在加拿大，低收入是食物无保障最有力的预测因素；在那里，每八户家庭中就有一户无法充分获得有营养的食物。
It’s well-established that food prices are an important determinant of food choice.
食物价格是食物选择的一个重要决定因素，这一点早有定论。
Low-income households report that they find it difficult to adopt dietary guidelines because food prices are a barrier to improving their diets.
低收入家庭表示，他们觉得很难采纳膳食指南，因为食物价格是他们改善饮食的障碍。
When researchers estimate the cost of diets people actually eat, higher-quality diets are typically more costly.
从研究人员对人们实际饮食成本的估算来看，质量较高的饮食通常更贵。
While this may be so, it does not, in itself, prove that healthy diets are necessarily more expensive or cost-prohibitive.
虽然情况或许如此，但这本身并不能证明健康饮食必然更贵，或贵得令人望而却步。
After all, not all socioeconomically disadvantaged people consume poor diets.
毕竟，并非所有社会经济地位处于弱势的人都吃得很差。
We can easily think of a number of foods and recipes that are both inexpensive and nutritious.
我们很容易就能想到不少既便宜又有营养的食物和食谱。
The internet is full of recipes for “eating well on a budget.”
网上到处都是“花小钱吃得好”的食谱。